A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1942-1949 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1946-1947 [1] (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1946-1947 [2] (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1948-1949 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1949-1950 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1949-1951 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1949-1951 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 122)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1950-1951 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1952-1954 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1953-1954 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: General, 1955-1956 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Records, 1940-1956 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Records, 1940-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 123)
- Virginia Museum Fellowships: Study re: Stipends, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1939-1948 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts in Roanoke, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts in Roanoke, 1947-1948 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 124)
- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts: Notes on, undated (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Virginia Museum Theatre, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Virginia Museum Theatre: Seventeenth Birthday Party, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Virginia Photographers 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1935-1936 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1959-1970 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Virginia Recreation Association, 1948-1954 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Virginia State Agencies, 1959-1969 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Virginia State Agencies: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Virginia State Agency Auxiliary, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Virginia State Agency Memos, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- Virginia State Agency Memos, 1974-1975 [1] (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Virginia State Agency Memos, 1974-1975 [2] (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Virginia State Board of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1947 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Virginia State Industrial Farm, 1956-1957 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Virginia State Library, 1935-1944 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Virginia State Library, 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 125)
- Virginia Teachers Association: Colored, 1949 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Virginia Town, 1951-1956 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Virginia Town, 1951-1956 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Virginia Union Choir, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Virginia World War II Memorial, 1950-1952 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Virginia World War II Memorial, 1951-1952 [1] (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Virginia World War II Memorial, 1951-1952 [2] (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Virginia World War II Memorial, 1951-1952 [2] (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Virginia World War II Memorial, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Virginia World War II Memorial: American Institute of Architects, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Virginia World War II Memorial: Invited Architects and Winner, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Virginia World War II Memorial: Jury, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Visitors Expected, 1963-1966 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- von Keller, Beatrice, 1935-1944 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- von Keller, Beatrice, 1942-1953 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Vose Galleries, 1956-1965 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- W: General, 1934-1940 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- W: General, 1945-1955 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- W: General, 1945-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 126)
- W: General, 1960-1968 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- W: General, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- W: General, 1970-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 127)
- W: General, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- W: General, 1972-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 128)
- Waddy, Mrs. Woodson P., 1951-1953 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Waddy, Mrs. Woodson P., 1951-1953 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Waddy, Mrs. Woodson P., 1951-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 129)
- Waddy Fountains, 1952-1955 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Walker, Clifford L., 1935-1941 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Walpole Society, 1963-1967 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- War Agencies, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- War Orders, 1939-1942 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Warburg, Edward M.M., 1957-1964 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Warner, L.C., II: Theatre Designer, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Wartime Emergency Measures, 1939-1943 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Washington, George: Portrait by Peale, 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Washington, George: Portrait by Peale, 1941-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 130)
- Washington and Lee University, 1949-1955 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Weddell, Alexander W., 1935-1945 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Weddell, Alexander W., 1945-1948 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Weddell, Alexander W., 1945-1948 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 131)
- Wednesday Evening Programs: 1947/48 Season, 1948 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Wednesday Evening Programs: 1948/49 Season, 1948-1949 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Wednesday Evening Programs: 1948/49 Season, 1948-1949 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Weeden Foundation, 1966-1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Weinhardt, Carl, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Weinhardt, Carl, 1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 132)
- West from Virginia, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- West Wing, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Westhampton Junior Women's Club: Tours for the Blind, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Wheelchairs for Galleries, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- White, John, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- White House Correspondence, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- White House Festival, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- White, Theo Ballou, 1934-1936 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Whitelaw, Robert N.S., 1955-1962 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Whitman, Thelma Cudlipp, 1935-1945 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Whitman, Thelma Cudlipp, 1935-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 133)
- Whitman, Thelma Cudlipp, 1945-1953 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Whitman, Thelma Cudlipp, 1945-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 134)
- Whitman, Thelma Cudlipp, 1951-1954 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Whitney, John Hay, 1961-1964 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Whitney Museum, 1935-1944 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Widder, Mr., 1955-1956 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Wilcox, Lois, 1934 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Wildenstein and Co., 1969-1972 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Wilder, Thornton, 1953-1965 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Will, Erwin H., 1965-1968 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- William and Mary Charter Day Ceremonies 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- William and Mary College, 1950-1965 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Williams, Mr. and Mrs. A.D., 1948-1952 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Williams, Mr. and Mrs. A.D., 1948-1952 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 135)
- Williams, Berkley, Jr., 1936-1944 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Williams, E. Randolph, 1935-1953 (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Williams, E. Randolph, 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- Williams, Fielding, 1958-1963 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Williams, Mrs. Walter A.J., 1954-1964 (Box 73, Folder 29)
- Williamsburg Reception Center, 1953-1954 (Box 73, Folder 30)
- Willingham, Mrs. William, 1949-1950 (Box 73, Folder 31)
- Willingham, Mrs. William, 1949-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 136)
- Wilmerdig, Lucius, Jr., 1954 (Box 73, Folder 32)
- Wilmerdig, Lucius, Jr., 1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 137)
- Wilson, Woodrow Birthplace Foundation, 1955-1959 (Box 73, Folder 33)
- Wilson, Woodrow Birthplace Foundation, 1955-1959 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 138)
- Winterthur Museum, 1957-1975 (Box 73, Folder 34)
- Woman's Auxiliary of the Medical Society of Virginia, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 35)
- Woman's Auxiliary to the Richmond Academy of Medicine, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 36)
- Woodlawn: Invitation List, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 37)
- Worcester Art Museum, 1935-1940 (Box 73, Folder 38)
- Worcester Art Museum, 1935-1940 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 139)
- Work Orders, 1949-1950 (Box 73, Folder 39)
- World's Fair Exhibit, 1938-1940 (Box 73, Folder 40)
- World's Fair Exhibition: Southern Preview, 1938-1939 (Box 73, Folder 41)
- Wright, Frank Lloyd Drawings, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 42)
- WRVA Radio and Television, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 43)
- Wyeth, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew, 1966-1968 (Box 73, Folder 44)
- Wyeth, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew, 1966-1968 (OVERSIZE) (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Wyeth, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew, 1966-1968 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 140)
- X, Y, Z: General, 1949-1972 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- X, Y, Z: General, 1949-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 141)
- Y, Z: General, 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Y, Z: General, 1973-1976 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Yale University, 1935-1945 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Yale University, 1958-1966 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Yale University: Committee, 1948-1950, folder 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Yale University: Committee, 1948-1950, folder 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Yale University: Council Committee, 1948-1954 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Yale University: Council Meeting, 1952-1954 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Yale University: Fine Arts Committee, 1948-1949, folder 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Yale University: Fine Arts Committee, 1948-1949, folder 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Yale University: Fine Arts Committee, 1950-1952 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Yale University: Fine Arts Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Yale University: Glee Club Concert, 1959-1961 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Zehmer, George B., 1935-1943 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: A: General, 1966-1972 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions: First Offers, 1935-1936 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions: Mrs. von Keller's File, 1941-1945 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1935-1950 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1935-1956 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1937-1945 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1950-1953 [1] (Box 75, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1950-1953 [2] (Box 75, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1953-1956 [1], folder 1 of 2 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1953-1956 [1], folder 2 of 2 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1953-1956 [2] (Box 75, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: General, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: Minutes (incomplete), 1935-1943 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: Minutes, 1945-1950 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Accessions Committee: 1973 January 9, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Acquisition Reports, 1940-1943 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Acquisitions: Possible, 1969-1973 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Acquisitions: Purchases, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: American Federation of Arts, 1945-1954 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: American Marine Painting, 1973-1977 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: American Painting: 1950 Special Traveling Exhibition, 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Anderson, Henry W., 1935-1944 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Anderson, Henry W., 1947-1948 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Anderson, Henry W., 1948-1954 (Box 75, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Anderson, Henry W., 1949-1954 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Annual Meeting: Board of Trustees, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Annual Reprt, 1942-1943: Worksheets, 1942-1943 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Annual Reports: Gallery Division, 1949/50-1954/55 (Box 75, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Archer, Edmund, 1935-1945 (Box 75, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Arrival Records, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Art Nouveau: Acquisitions, 1971-1973 (Box 75, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Artmobile: Operations, 1953-1956 (Box 75, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Arts in Virginia: Search for Designer, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: B: General, 1973-1976 (Box 75, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Ballet, Arthur H., 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Barry, Iris, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Beam, Kenneth M., Assistant Administrator, 1974-1976 (Box 75, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Bellows, Mrs. George W., 1944 (Box 75, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Annual Meeting 1945, 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Annual Meeting, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Annual Meeting 1952 May 31, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Annual Meeting, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: General, 1937-1956 (Box 75, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: General, 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Minutes, 1934-1943 (Box 75, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Special Meeting 1950 October 27, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Board of Trustees: Special Meeting 1956 January 29, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Boston Museum of Fine Arts, 1947-1954 (Box 75, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Bowditch, Vincent, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Branch, Blythe W., 1934-1937 (Box 75, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Branch, Blythe W., 1937-1938 (Box 75, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Branch, Blythe W., 1938-1939 (Box 75, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Branch, Blythe W., 1941-1942 [1] (Box 75, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Branch, Blythe W., 1941-1942 [2] (Box 75, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Brown, James M., 1974-1976 (Box 75, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Bruce, Alisa Mellon Estate, 1970-1973 (Box 75, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Bruce, David K.E., 1948-1953 (Box 75, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Brummer Collection, 1965-1966 (Box 75, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Brussels Universal and International Exposition: Sculpture, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Bryan, John Stewart, 1935-1944 (Box 75, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Buchholtz Gallery, 1946-1952 (Box 75, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Architects, 1947-1955 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Commitment for Galleries, 1944-1949 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Floor Plan, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Building: French Terra Cotta Figures, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Gallery Floor Plan, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Mural, 1954-1955 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Photos of Drawings, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Building: South Wing - Layout, 1964-1966 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Building: Theatre - Photographs and Floor Plans, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Building and Grounds Committee: Pending, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Building Committee: General, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: C: General, 1962-1972 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: C: General, 1973-1976 [2] (Box 76, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Ca-Cl, 1945-1954 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Ca-Cl, 1959-1965 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Caligula, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Carbons, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Carnegie Institute, 1935-1944 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Catherwood Foundation Fellowship and Virginia Museum Fellowships: Gaines, William R., 1956-1957 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Christison, Mrs.: Correspondence, Misc., 1949-1952 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Christison, Mrs.: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 76, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Chronological (Correspondence), 1975 (Box 76, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Chronological File, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Chrysler Museum: Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Collections, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions, 1951-1953 (Box 76, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [1] (Box 76, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [2] (Box 76, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions, 1953-1954 [3] (Box 76, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions 1952, 1948-1952 (Box 76, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Collection: Possible Additions 1954 (3), 1952-1954 (Box 76, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Colt, Thomas C., Jr., 1935-1955 (Box 76, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 76, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1952-1956 (Box 76, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 76, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1958-1969 (Box 76, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Correspondence: Velz, 1955-1956 (Box 76, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Council, 1955-1956 (Box 76, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Council: Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 76, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Council of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1969-1972 (Box 76, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: D: General, 1949-1955 (Box 76, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: D: General, 1958-1972 (Box 76, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Davenport, Carson, 1935-1944 (Box 76, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1935-1944 (Box 76, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Davis, Mrs. Lincoln, 1945-1955 (Box 76, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Day, Elizabeth Nottingham, 1934-1945 (Box 76, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Day, Mr. and Mrs. Horace, 1945-1954 (Box 76, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Division Head Memos, 1946-1973 (Box 76, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Division Head Memos, 1969-1972 (Box 76, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Donations and Gifts, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Donations to the Museum, 1964-1972 (Box 76, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Donations, Contributions, Gifts, 1971-1973 (Box 76, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Donations, Contributions, Gifts,etc., 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: duPont, Mrs. Alfred I., 1958-1968 (Box 76, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: E: General, 1945-1972 (Box 76, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Egyptian Gallery Opening 1961 April 14, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Events: National Conference of Editorial Writers, 1958-1960 (Box 76, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Events: Virginia Artists Jury 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 76, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1949-1952 (Box 76, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1950-1953 (Box 76, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 63)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1954-1955 (Box 76, Folder 64)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [1] (Box 76, Folder 65)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1955-1956 [2] (Box 76, Folder 66)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: General, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 67)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 76, Folder 68)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 76, Folder 69)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes, 1953-1955 (Box 76, Folder 70)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Minutes, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 71)
- RESTRICTED: Executive Committee: Pending, 1951-1956 (Box 76, Folder 72)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: 25th Anniversary - Treasures of America, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Collector of the Year 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Davies, Arthur B., 1963 January 11 - February 10, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Greek Gold (Treasures from Alexander), 1963-1966 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Gund Collection of Western Art Preview, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Homer, Winslow, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: In Virginia, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Old Master Painting 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Treasures from the Pierpont Morgan Library, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Exhibitions: Two Sculptors - Lipton and Lachaise, 1971-1972 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Camp Pickett Post Library, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Christchurch School, 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Colonial High School, Blue Ridge, VA, 1951-1952 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Culpeper County High School, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Dahlgren School, US Naval Proving Ground, Dahlgren VA, 1950-1954 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Danville Art Association, 1951-1952 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Danville Wednesday Club, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Dinwiddie Woman's Club, 1950-1954 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Fairfax Hall Junior College, 1949-1951 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Farmville State Teachers College/Longwood College, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Ginter Park Woman's Club, 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Graves, Ken Studio, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Henrico County Public Schools, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Independence Woman's Club, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Jonesville Woman's Club, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Loudoun Community College, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Lynchburg College, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Lynchburg Woman's Club, 1951-1955 (Box 77, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Martinsville City Schools, 1951-1952 (Box 77, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: McHarg School PTA, Radford, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Petersburg - Fine Arts School, 1951-1954 (Box 77, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Petersburg Federated Woman's Club, 1948-1951 (Box 77, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Petersburg High School, 1949-1951 (Box 77, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Poquoson Senior Woman's Club, 1948-1950 (Box 77, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Randolph-Macon College, Ashland, 1948-1949 (Box 77, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Richmond Professional Institutte, 1947-1949 (Box 77, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Rockingham County Public Schools, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Scottsville High School, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Stony Creek Woman's Club, 1947-1952 (Box 77, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: University of Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1934-1949 (Box 77, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Extension Department: Wilson-Jackson PTA, Waynesboro, 1947-1953 (Box 77, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: F: General, 1955-1967 (Box 77, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: F: General, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Faberge Collection: Installation, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Finance Committee: General, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Finances, 1969-1972 (Box 77, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: First and Merchants Trusts, 1969-1972 (Box 77, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Fitzroy Memorial, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Fogg Art Museum, 1935-1943 (Box 77, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: French and Company, 1946-1959 (Box 77, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: G: General, 1953-1971 (Box 77, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Gaines, Bill: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Galleries: General, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Garbish, Col. Edgar, 1949-1958 (Box 77, Folder 56)